anime-ds.com 2011-11-27

# Anime - Download Stream: Privacy Policy

This privacy policy covers the site www.Anime-DS.com. Because we want to demonstrate our commitment to our users’ privacy, we disclose the following information. 

1\. What personally identifiable information Anime-DS.com collects.  
---  
2\. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.  
3\. What organization collects the information.  
4\. How Anime-DS.com uses the information.  
5\. With whom Anime-DS.com may share user information.  
6\. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.  
7\. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Anime-DS.com control.  
8\. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.  

## Information Collection and Use

Anime-DS.com is the sole owner of the infomation collected on our web site. Anime-DS.com collects information at several different points on our Web site.Information is collected for the purpose of tracking hits/views on a daily basis. A user must provide the clickstream information (internet protocol address, internet service provider, platform type, date/time stamp, operating system), http protocol information (last uri requested and browser type), unique identifiers (login id or other id), search terms (search text), transaction information (account transactions), user's name, user's birthdate, user's login information and user's gender (male or female). It is optional for the user to provide User's Name, User's Birthdate and User's Gender (Male or Female). We encourage users to provide optional information so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. The reason we use this information is to complete the current transaction. We retain this information only as long as required to complete the action that required the information to be collected. Cookies  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. You can set your browser to notify you to either accept or deny the cookie.

Our website uses cookies to enhance our site.

## Profiles

Anime-DS.com only creates user profiles for the purpose of showing username and other users may send private messages.

## Communications from the Site

Customer Service  
If there is a problem with a user's website, we contact them to resolve the problem.

## Sharing Information

Legal Disclaimer  
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. Personally Identifiable Information  
Personally identifiable information is not shared with any third parties. Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)  
Aggregate information is not shared with any third parties.

## Data Security

Anime-DS.com has physical security in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of information. Our company does not handle sensitive financial or health related information.

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes such as zip code, phone, email or postal address they can change other information. If a user wishes to correct/update information or no longer desires our service, they can notify us of what they desire by contacting us using any of the information in the Contact section of this policy.

## Links and Advertisements

Our website contains links to other sites. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. We, Anime-DS.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## Changes to the Privacy Statement

The information you submit to us is controlled by the privacy policy in effect at the time you submit it. If we significantly change our policy, we will reserve the right to apply this change to any and all data previously collected before the change was made.

## Contact Information

Using the following information, you can contact us if you have questions about our privacy policy.

## Resolving Privacy Policy Disputes

If you think we have not followed our privacy policy in some way, it can be resolved in the following manner.
